nottingham.edu.cn 2019-10-09

# Privacy - The University of Nottingham Ningbo China - 宁波诺丁汉大学

## General

References in this privacy policy to "we", "our" and "us", etc. are references to us, The University of Nottingham.

We are committed to protecting your privacy and respecting the confidentiality of information which you provide when you visit our website at [www.nottingham.edu.cn](http://www.nottingham.edu.cn/). At the same time, we want to try to ensure that you obtain full value from our website and from the services which you may want to receive via our website.

You should read this privacy policy in conjunction with our website terms of use, of which this privacy policy forms a part. By agreeing to our terms of use, you are consenting to our processing of your personal data in accordance with this privacy policy. Any changes to this privacy policy will be posted on our website and, where appropriate, notified to you by email.

## The information we collect

It is possible to use our website without providing any personal data. However, we may automatically collect certain information about you when you use our website, including by our "cookies" (see below), such as the IP address of your computer and the dates and times of your visits.

In some areas of our website we may ask you for personal data, such as your name, address and email details, that will enable us to make your site visit a more rewarding experience for you and/or to contact you after your visit. Examples of this might be where you complete an online form asking for a copy of a prospectus or to book a place on an open day with us, where you ask for information about a job vacancy, or where you subscribe to an online newsletter.

In some other areas of our website, where you can register as an online user, we may ask you for more detailed information about yourself. In order to provide these types of services, it may be necessary for us to collect and process additional personal data, such as information about your educational history.

## How we may use this information

Personal data which we collect about you via our website is held on and processed by computers situated at The University of Nottingham. We will retain this data for a reasonable period or for as long as the law requires.

We will not disclose any of your personal data collected via our website to any third party, other than in circumstances set out in this privacy policy and/or where you have given us permission to do so, unless we are required to do so by law.

We may use personal data collected from you via our website to manage and monitor use of our website. Otherwise, we will only use this personal data for the purposes for which it was collected, unless you have given us permission to use it for other stated purposes. For example, if you supply us with your name and address so we can send you a prospectus for a particular department, and at the same time you agree that we may send you similar information in the future, we may subsequently invite you to an open day at that department.

If at any time you want to withdraw any permission you have given us to provide you  with services, or to use your personal data in any other way, please inform us by email.

## Cookies

Where you visit our website we may send "cookies" to the browser on your computer, even if you do not provide us with any personal data. Cookies enable us to recognise you (by a unique number allocated to you) when you return to our website and so to personalise your return by, for example, customising web pages based on which areas of the website were previously of interest to you. If you have previously provided us with personal data, then cookies may enable us automatically to fill in your name and other information when, for example, you complete an online form.

Cookies also enable us to compile anonymous, aggregated statistics which help us understand our our website is used and so how we may improve it. It is not possible for cookies to read personal information on your computer and/or to find out any personal information about you. However, you can refuse to accept cookies by modifying the settings in your browser, but this may limit the functionality of web pages on our website, or your access to our website.

## Security

Our website and our computer systems have security measures in place with the aim of protecting the loss, misuse or alteration of personal data held by us.

## Other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this privacy policy. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of any such linked websites.

## Comments or questions

Please send any comments or questions relating to this privacy policy to our [Webmaster](mailto:scott.mallinson@nottingham.edu.cn "Email the webmaster").
